<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Infrastructure on Juniqe Cloud And Infrastruture Documentation</title>
    <link>https://juniqe.gitlab.io/devops/docs/infra/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Infrastructure on Juniqe Cloud And Infrastruture Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>asdrubal@juniqe.com (Asdrubal Gonzalez Penton)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>asdrubal@juniqe.com (Asdrubal Gonzalez Penton)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 13:30:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juniqe.gitlab.io/devops/docs/infra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloud &amp; Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://juniqe.gitlab.io/devops/docs/infra/first-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 13:43:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>asdrubal@juniqe.com (Asdrubal Gonzalez Penton)</author>
      <guid>https://juniqe.gitlab.io/devops/docs/infra/first-content/</guid>
      <description>Environments We run our servers in different environments (separate AWS accounts). These are:
juniqe-production juniqe-staging juniqe-integration (currently not in use) Deployments We follow the following motos for all our deployments:
Application infrastructure should be managed and deployed as part of the application code. All deployments should be implemented with CI/CD in mind. FreatureBranching should be automated and be part of the CI/CD. Any change to our applications is currently going through the following steps:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Entrypoints</title>
      <link>https://juniqe.gitlab.io/devops/docs/infra/devops-entrypoints/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 13:43:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <author>asdrubal@juniqe.com (Asdrubal Gonzalez Penton)</author>
      <guid>https://juniqe.gitlab.io/devops/docs/infra/devops-entrypoints/</guid>
      <description>New accounts [on/off] boarding VPN management: Production VPN MySQL users: SSO: Providers Cognito - no actions are needed. Commercetools MC SSO: CommerceTools SSO. Google Groups. On GSuite new Engineering accounts should be added to these groups:
All Engineering For DevOps also the group: DevOps GitLab and Sentry: access should be granted to the projects
Infrastructure management New infrastructure on K8s is documented in: cloud repository
Everything around K8s DNS management for the cluster K8s IAM ALB for K8s BI infrastructure The old part of the infrastructure is in: juniqe-infra</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
